[
    { "question" : "行く", "answer" : "to go", "pronunciation" : "iku", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "来る", "answer" : "to come", "pronunciation" : "kuru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "見る", "answer" : "to see", "pronunciation" : "miru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "聞く", "answer" : "to listen", "pronunciation" : "kiku", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "言う", "answer" : "to say", "pronunciation" : "iu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "する", "answer" : "to do", "pronunciation" : "suru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "食べる", "answer" : "to eat", "pronunciation" : "taberu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "飲む", "answer" : "to drink", "pronunciation" : "nomu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "起きる", "answer" : "to wake up", "pronunciation" : "okiru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "寝る", "answer" : "to sleep", "pronunciation" : "neru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "話す", "answer" : "to speak", "pronunciation" : "hanasu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "待つ", "answer" : "to wait", "pronunciation" : "matsu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "会う", "answer" : "to meet", "pronunciation" : "au", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "教える", "answer" : "to teach", "pronunciation" : "oshieru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "帰る", "answer" : "to return", "pronunciation" : "kaeru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "買う", "answer" : "to buy", "pronunciation" : "kau", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "売る", "answer" : "to sell", "pronunciation" : "uru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "作る", "answer" : "to make", "pronunciation" : "tsukuru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "持つ", "answer" : "to hold", "pronunciation" : "motsu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "忘れる", "answer" : "to forget", "pronunciation" : "wasureru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "覚える", "answer" : "to remember", "pronunciation" : "oboeru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "遊ぶ", "answer" : "to play", "pronunciation" : "asobu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "泳ぐ", "answer" : "to swim", "pronunciation" : "oyogu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "歩く", "answer" : "to walk", "pronunciation" : "aruku", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "走る", "answer" : "to run", "pronunciation" : "hashiru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "乗る", "answer" : "to ride", "pronunciation" : "noru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "下る", "answer" : "to go down", "pronunciation" : "kudaru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "上がる", "answer" : "to go up", "pronunciation" : "agaru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "入る", "answer" : "to enter", "pronunciation" : "hairu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "出る", "answer" : "to exit", "pronunciation" : "deru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "手伝う", "answer" : "to help", "pronunciation" : "tetsudau", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "洗う", "answer" : "to wash", "pronunciation" : "arau", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "着る", "answer" : "to wear", "pronunciation" : "kiru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "脱ぐ", "answer" : "to take off", "pronunciation" : "nugu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "掃除する", "answer" : "to clean", "pronunciation" : "souji suru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "歌う", "answer" : "to sing", "pronunciation" : "utau", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "踊る", "answer" : "to dance", "pronunciation" : "odoru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "笑う", "answer" : "to laugh", "pronunciation" : "warau", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "泣く", "answer" : "to cry", "pronunciation" : "naku", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "描く", "answer" : "to draw", "pronunciation" : "egaku", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "読む", "answer" : "to read", "pronunciation" : "yomu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "書く", "answer" : "to write", "pronunciation" : "kaku", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "選ぶ", "answer" : "to choose", "pronunciation" : "erabu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "見つける", "answer" : "to find", "pronunciation" : "mitsukeru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "捨てる", "answer" : "to throw away", "pronunciation" : "suteru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "飛ぶ", "answer" : "to fly", "pronunciation" : "tobu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "勝つ", "answer" : "to win", "pronunciation" : "katsu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "負ける", "answer" : "to lose", "pronunciation" : "makeru", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "踏む", "answer" : "to step on", "pronunciation" : "fumu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "調べる", "answer" : "to investigate", "pronunciation" : "shiraberu", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "人", "answer" : "person", "pronunciation" : "hito", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "家族", "answer" : "family", "pronunciation" : "kazoku", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "友達", "answer" : "friend", "pronunciation" : "tomodachi", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "学校", "answer" : "school", "pronunciation" : "gakkou", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "仕事", "answer" : "work", "pronunciation" : "shigoto", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "本", "answer" : "book", "pronunciation" : "hon", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "新聞", "answer" : "newspaper", "pronunciation" : "shinbun", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "雑誌", "answer" : "magazine", "pronunciation" : "zasshi", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "食べ物", "answer" : "food", "pronunciation" : "tabemono", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "飲み物", "answer" : "drink", "pronunciation" : "nomimono", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "服", "answer" : "clothes", "pronunciation" : "fuku", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "靴", "answer" : "shoes", "pronunciation" : "kutsu", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "車", "answer" : "car", "pronunciation" : "kuruma", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "自転車", "answer" : "bicycle", "pronunciation" : "jitensha", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "電車", "answer" : "train", "pronunciation" : "densha", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "飛行機", "answer" : "airplane", "pronunciation" : "hikouki", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "船", "answer" : "ship", "pronunciation" : "fune", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "家", "answer" : "house", "pronunciation" : "ie", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "部屋", "answer" : "room", "pronunciation" : "heya", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ベッド", "answer" : "bed", "pronunciation" : "beddo", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "椅子", "answer" : "chair", "pronunciation" : "isu", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "机", "answer" : "desk", "pronunciation" : "tsukue", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "テーブル", "answer" : "table", "pronunciation" : "teeburu", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "電話", "answer" : "telephone", "pronunciation" : "denwa", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "スマートフォン", "answer" : "smartphone", "pronunciation" : "sumaato fon", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "パソコン", "answer" : "personal computer", "pronunciation" : "pasokon", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "テレビ", "answer" : "television", "pronunciation" : "terebi", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "カメラ", "answer" : "camera", "pronunciation" : "kamera", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "時計", "answer" : "watch", "pronunciation" : "tokei", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "お金", "answer" : "money", "pronunciation" : "okane", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "財布", "answer" : "wallet", "pronunciation" : "saifu", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "銀行", "answer" : "bank", "pronunciation" : "ginkou", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "レストラン", "answer" : "restaurant", "pronunciation" : "resutoran", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "スーパー", "answer" : "supermarket", "pronunciation" : "suupaa", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "病院", "answer" : "hospital", "pronunciation" : "byouin", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "薬局", "answer" : "pharmacy", "pronunciation" : "yakkyoku", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "公園", "answer" : "park", "pronunciation" : "kouen", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "市場", "answer" : "market", "pronunciation" : "ichiba", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "街", "answer" : "town", "pronunciation" : "machi", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "地下鉄", "answer" : "subway", "pronunciation" : "chikatetsu", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "空港", "answer" : "airport", "pronunciation" : "kuukou", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "駅", "answer" : "station", "pronunciation" : "eki", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "道路", "answer" : "road", "pronunciation" : "douro", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "橋", "answer" : "bridge", "pronunciation" : "hashi", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "川", "answer" : "river", "pronunciation" : "kawa", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "海", "answer" : "sea", "pronunciation" : "umi", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "山", "answer" : "mountain", "pronunciation" : "yama", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "空", "answer" : "sky", "pronunciation" : "sora", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "太陽", "answer" : "sun", "pronunciation" : "taiyou", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "月", "answer" : "moon", "pronunciation" : "tsuki", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "星", "answer" : "star", "pronunciation" : "hoshi", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "宇宙", "answer" : "universe", "pronunciation" : "uchuu", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "花", "answer" : "flower", "pronunciation" : "hana", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "木", "answer" : "tree", "pronunciation" : "ki", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "果物", "answer" : "fruit", "pronunciation" : "kudamono", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "暑い", "answer" : "hot", "pronunciation" : "atsui", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "寒い", "answer" : "cold", "pronunciation" : "samui", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "新しい", "answer" : "new", "pronunciation" : "atarashii", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "古い", "answer" : "old", "pronunciation" : "furui", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "良い", "answer" : "good", "pronunciation" : "ii", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "悪い", "answer" : "bad", "pronunciation" : "warui", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "高い", "answer" : "high", "pronunciation" : "takai", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "低い", "answer" : "low", "pronunciation" : "hikui", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "大きい", "answer" : "big", "pronunciation" : "ookii", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "小さい", "answer" : "small", "pronunciation" : "chiisai", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "暖かい", "answer" : "warm", "pronunciation" : "atatakai", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "冷たい", "answer" : "cool", "pronunciation" : "tsumetai", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "美味しい", "answer" : "delicious", "pronunciation" : "umai", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "不味い", "answer" : "bad-tasting", "pronunciation" : "mazui", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "甘い", "answer" : "sweet", "pronunciation" : "amai", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "辛い", "answer" : "spicy", "pronunciation" : "karai", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "塩辛い", "answer" : "salty", "pronunciation" : "shoppai", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "苦い", "answer" : "bitter", "pronunciation" : "nigai", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "すっきりする", "answer" : "refreshing", "pronunciation" : "sukkiri suru", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "眠い", "answer" : "sleepy", "pronunciation" : "nemui", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "疲れた", "answer" : "tired", "pronunciation" : "tsukareta", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "元気な", "answer" : "energetic", "pronunciation" : "genkina", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "簡単な", "answer" : "easy", "pronunciation" : "kantan na", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "難しい", "answer" : "difficult", "pronunciation" : "muzukashii", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "綺麗な", "answer" : "pretty", "pronunciation" : "kireina", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "可愛い", "answer" : "cute", "pronunciation" : "kawaii", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "静かな", "answer" : "quiet", "pronunciation" : "shizuka na", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "賑やかな", "answer" : "lively", "pronunciation" : "nigiyaka na", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "不思議な", "answer" : "mysterious", "pronunciation" : "fushigi na", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "曖昧な", "answer" : "vague", "pronunciation" : "aimai na", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "はっきりした", "answer" : "clear", "pronunciation" : "hakkiri shita", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "キラキラした", "answer" : "sparkling", "pronunciation" : "kirakira shita", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "真っ白な", "answer" : "pure white", "pronunciation" : "masshiro na", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "黒い", "answer" : "black", "pronunciation" : "kuroi", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "赤い", "answer" : "red", "pronunciation" : "akai", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "青い", "answer" : "blue", "pronunciation" : "aoi", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "黄色い", "answer" : "yellow", "pronunciation" : "kiiroi", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "緑の", "answer" : "green", "pronunciation" : "midori no", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "白い", "answer" : "white", "pronunciation" : "shiroi", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "格好いい", "answer" : "cool", "pronunciation" : "kakkoii", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "可哀想な", "answer" : "pitiful", "pronunciation" : "kawaisou na", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "羨ましい", "answer" : "envious", "pronunciation" : "urayamashii", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "悲しい", "answer" : "sad", "pronunciation" : "kanashii", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "危ない", "answer" : "dangerous", "pronunciation" : "abunai", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "本当の", "answer" : "genuine", "pronunciation" : "hontou no", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "同じ", "answer" : "same", "pronunciation" : "onaji", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "素晴らしい", "answer" : "wonderful", "pronunciation" : "subarashii", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "あまり", "answer" : "not much", "pronunciation" : "amari", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "今", "answer" : "now", "pronunciation" : "ima", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "もう", "answer" : "already", "pronunciation" : "mou", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "まだ", "answer" : "still", "pronunciation" : "mada", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "すぐに", "answer" : "immediately", "pronunciation" : "sugu ni", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "たくさん", "answer" : "a lot", "pronunciation" : "takusan", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ちょっと", "answer" : "a little bit", "pronunciation" : "chotto", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "よく", "answer" : "well", "pronunciation" : "yoku", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "だいたい", "answer" : "mostly", "pronunciation" : "daitai", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ちゃんと", "answer" : "properly", "pronunciation" : "chanto", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "とても", "answer" : "very", "pronunciation" : "totemo", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ある程度", "answer" : "to a certain extent", "pronunciation" : "aruteido", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "必ず", "answer" : "without fail", "pronunciation" : "kanarazu", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "あっという間に", "answer" : "in the blink of an eye", "pronunciation" : "atto iu ma ni", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "たしかに", "answer" : "surely", "pronunciation" : "tashika ni", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ゆっくり", "answer" : "slowly", "pronunciation" : "yukkuri", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "早く", "answer" : "quickly", "pronunciation" : "hayaku", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "まず", "answer" : "first of all", "pronunciation" : "mazu", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "いつも", "answer" : "always", "pronunciation" : "itsumo", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "結構", "answer" : "fine", "pronunciation" : "kekko", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "だんだん", "answer" : "gradually", "pronunciation" : "dandan", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "めっちゃ", "answer" : "really", "pronunciation" : "meccha", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "やはり", "answer" : "as expected", "pronunciation" : "yahari", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "あらかじめ", "answer" : "in advance", "pronunciation" : "arakajime", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "大体", "answer" : "mostly", "pronunciation" : "daitai", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "しばらく", "answer" : "for a while", "pronunciation" : "shibaraku", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "たしか", "answer" : "for sure", "pronunciation" : "tashika", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "まあまあ", "answer" : "so-so", "pronunciation" : "maamaa", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ずっと", "answer" : "all the time", "pronunciation" : "zutto", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "きちんと", "answer" : "properly", "pronunciation" : "kichinto", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "もしかしたら", "answer" : "perhaps", "pronunciation" : "moshikashitara", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "いっぱい", "answer" : "full", "pronunciation" : "ippai", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ひどく", "answer" : "terribly", "pronunciation" : "hidoku", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "やっぱり", "answer" : "as expected", "pronunciation" : "yappari", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "どんどん", "answer" : "steadily", "pronunciation" : "dondon", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "たちまち", "answer" : "immediately", "pronunciation" : "tachimachi", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "うまく", "answer" : "skillfully", "pronunciation" : "umaku", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "だいぶ", "answer" : "considerably", "pronunciation" : "daibu", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "すっかり", "answer" : "completely", "pronunciation" : "sukkari", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "まさか", "answer" : "no way", "pronunciation" : "masaka", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "そうそう", "answer" : "exactly", "pronunciation" : "sousou", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "もっと", "answer" : "more", "pronunciation" : "motto", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "いくら", "answer" : "how much", "pronunciation" : "ikura", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "そして", "answer" : "and", "pronunciation" : "soshite", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "だから", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "dakara", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "しかし", "answer" : "however", "pronunciation" : "shikashi", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "また", "answer" : "also", "pronunciation" : "mata", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "それに", "answer" : "moreover", "pronunciation" : "sore ni", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "だけど", "answer" : "however", "pronunciation" : "dakedo", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "なので", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "nanode", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "なぜなら", "answer" : "because", "pronunciation" : "nazenara", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "でも", "answer" : "but", "pronunciation" : "demo", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "なら", "answer" : "if", "pronunciation" : "nara", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ところで", "answer" : "by the way", "pronunciation" : "tokorode", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "というのは", "answer" : "that is to say", "pronunciation" : "to iu no wa", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ときに", "answer" : "sometimes", "pronunciation" : "toki ni", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "それで", "answer" : "so", "pronunciation" : "sore de", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "つまり", "answer" : "in other words", "pronunciation" : "tsumari", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "あるいは", "answer" : "or", "pronunciation" : "aruiwa", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "それから", "answer" : "and then", "pronunciation" : "sorekara", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "なかでも", "answer" : "among them", "pronunciation" : "nakademo", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "とりあえず", "answer" : "for the time being", "pronunciation" : "toriaezu", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ただ", "answer" : "only", "pronunciation" : "tada", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "または", "answer" : "or", "pronunciation" : "matawa", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "なお", "answer" : "furthermore", "pronunciation" : "nao", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "あるがまま", "answer" : "as it is", "pronunciation" : "arugamama", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "たしかに", "answer" : "certainly", "pronunciation" : "tashikani", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "それとも", "answer" : "or", "pronunciation" : "soretomo", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "まず", "answer" : "first of all", "pronunciation" : "mazu", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "なんと", "answer" : "what", "pronunciation" : "nanto", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "そのため", "answer" : "for that reason", "pronunciation" : "sono tame", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "あくまでも", "answer" : "to the end", "pronunciation" : "akuma demo", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "なぜか", "answer" : "for some reason", "pronunciation" : "nazeka", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "一方で", "answer" : "on the other hand", "pronunciation" : "ippou de", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "それでも", "answer" : "but", "pronunciation" : "soredemo", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "いっぽう", "answer" : "on one hand", "pronunciation" : "ippou", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "しかしながら", "answer" : "however", "pronunciation" : "shikashinagara", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ついでに", "answer" : "incidentally", "pronunciation" : "tsuide ni", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "および", "answer" : "as well as", "pronunciation" : "oyobi", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "かつ", "answer" : "and", "pronunciation" : "katsu", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ことによると", "answer" : "depending on", "pronunciation" : "koto ni yoru to", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ということで", "answer" : "that being the case", "pronunciation" : "to iu koto de", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" }
]